

About Me

I am a software engineer with a background in sales. I use my experience with leadership in combination with problem solving to help accelerate my career in Software Engineering. My background enables me to approach each project with keen insight into efficiently solving problems, while collaborating with others to create and offer the best product in a timely manner.

Employment History

Hospitality Associate, MedMen, Los Angeles

NOVEMBER 2019 - MAY 2020

- Met/exceeded personal sales volume and KPI goals
- Added value to the team by being authentic and confident self-leader who strives to execute our world class hospitality program
- Brought in repeat business through strong local grassroots networking, customer data capture and our loyalty program
- Executed high customer experience standards and industry leading customer engagement through strong sales techniques and product knowledge

Owner Advisor, Tesla, Los Angeles

OCTOBER 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2019

- Greet customers to determine make, type, and quality of vehicle desired to best suit needs and lifestyle
- Display creativity / ingenuity in presenting solutions (financial, technical, lifestyle, practical) to customers
- Demonstrate mastery of products offered by Tesla in order to conduct product consultations and test drives
- Manage accounts in Salesforce for current and potential clients
- Maintain relationships with clients to increase brand loyalty and build upon rapport
- Contribute to nationally ranked Tesla branch tracking 140% over sales goal

Education

Software Engineer Immersive, General Assembly, Los Angeles

MAY 2020 - AUGUST 2020

General Assembly is an experiential educational institution that offers. a leading-edge curriculum from expert instructors that prepares the next generation of career professionals.

- Learned core skills to build full-stack web aplications.
- created strong conceptual wireframes that allowed for clear project management and group steering.
- Learned to effectively communicate and collaborate with UX, clients and other software engineers.

Georgia State University, Atlanta

AUGUST 2014 - MAY 2016

Business Administration

Contact

(404) 323-8071 wwadams94@gmail.com

Links

Github

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Portfolio

Skills

JavaScript

C++

Python

Django

jQuery

React.js

HTML/CSS